Guide to the Daniel Rubin Papers TAM.657
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Education Department, 1930s-1997; 19.5 Linear Feet in 34 manuscript boxes, 2 record cartons, and 3 cassette boxes; 6 audiocassettes
  - National Board and Secretariat: Education, Ideological Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 126, Folder 6-7)
  - National Cadre Schools, 1969-1978 (Box 126, Folder 8-10)
  - National Communist Party School, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 11-12)
  - National Party School, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - National Party School and National Education Work, 1969-1970 (Box 230, Folder 2-4)
  - National Question, Theory, Lenin, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - National Question Materials, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - National School, 1967-1985 (Box 127, Folder 3-10)
  - National School, 1985-1987 (Box 128, Folder 1-5)
  - National School, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 5-6)
  - National School: Arrangements, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - National School: Curriculum, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - National School: Daily, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - National School: Diploma of Graduation, 1981 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - National School: Home School, 1978 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - National School: Introduction, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 1-2)
  - National School: Evaluation, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - National School: Final Event, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - National School: Food, Housing, Finances, Hall, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - National School: Materials Done, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - National School: Notes, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - National School: Notes and Discussion Topics, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 12)
  - National School: Notes and Memos to Participants, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - National School: Organizing, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 14)
  - National School: Outlines, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 6-10)
  - National School: Outlines, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 1-3)
  - National School: Opening, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - National School: Recruiting, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - National School: Recruiting (Called Off), 1987 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - National School: Reading Lists, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - National School: Reading Material, 8 Weeks, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 8-10)
  - National School: Readings and Discussion Notes, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 15)
  - National School: Registrations, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 16)
  - National School: Registrations, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - National School: Rules and Curriculum, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - National School: Rules and Curriculum, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - National School: Schedule and Discussions, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 17)
  - National School: Schedules, 1967-1978 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - National School: School Opening, 8 Weeks, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - National School: School Outline, 1960s-1970s (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - National School: School Record, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 5-7)
  - National School: Student Questions, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 18)
  - National School: Teachers, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 8-9)
  - New Members, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - New Members Class: Brooklyn, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - New Members Class: New York District, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - New Members Class Outline, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - New Members Outline, 1982-1983 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - New Members Outline, 1982-1987 (Box 132, Folder 1-4)
  - New Questions: Marxist-Lenin Theory, 1986 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - New York District Leadership Seminars, 1982 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - New York District Seminars, 1982 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - New York and Public Marxist Schools, 1984-1989 (Box 132, Folder 8-10)
  - New York and Public Marxist Schools, 1984-1989 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - New York Regional School, 1989-1990 (Box 133, Folder 2-3)
  - Other Public Left Schools and Publications, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 4-5)
  - Party Builder Edits, undated (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Party Standards, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Party Theory of Education, 1971 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Peace Education for New York, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - People's Daily World Classes, 1982 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Plan for Schools, 1981-1984 (Box 133, Folder 11-13)
  - Plan of Work: Department Draft, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Plan of Work: Department Outlines, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Political Bureau: Educational Discussions, 1983 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Political Economy, 1968-1991 (Box 134, Folder 4-6)
  - Public Marxist Schools/El Instituto del Pueblo, 1982-1985 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Public National School, 1988 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Readings: "Communism the Philosophy of Humanism", 1987 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Readings on Labor, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Readings on Peace, 1983-1985 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Readings on Socialism, 1984-1986 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Readings on Spain, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Readings on Race, 1981-1987 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Readings on Women's Equality, undated (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Review of Schools, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Regional Curriculum, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Regional Literature Arrangements, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Regional Schools, 1983 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Regional Schools, 1983-1990 (Box 136, Folder 1-6)
  - Regional Schools, 1989 (Box 230, Folder 19-20)
  - Regional Schools: Boston, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Regional Schools: California, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Regional Schools: Evaluations, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Regional Schools Materials, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 1-3)
  - Regional Schools: Midwest, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Regional Schools: New York, 1983-1985 (Box 137, Folder 5-6)
  - Regional Schools: Ohio, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Regional Schools: Outlines, 1989 (Box 230, Folder 21)
  - Regional Schools: Participant Outline, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Regional Schools: Recruiting, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Regional Schools: Registration, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Regional Schools: Registration Forms and Inventory of Materials Sent to Schools in New York, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Regional Schools: San Francisco, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Regional Schools: Summer, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 1-3)
  - Regional Schools: Teacher Guide, 1989 (Box 230, Folder 22)
  - Sample Leaflets and Flyers: How to Make Leaflets, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Schools Report, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - School Outlines, 1940s-1950s (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Shop Papers, 1983-1987 (Box 230, Folder 23)
  - Socialist Theory and Other Unread Theory, 1988-1990 (Box 138, Folder 7-8)
  - Source Materials on USSR Relations with East Asia, 1950 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Source Material on Korean Political and Ideologies, 1950 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Study Groups, 1986-1987, undated (Box 139, Folder 3-4)
  - Strategy and Tactics, 1981, undated (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Study Group on Socialist Countries: Park Slope, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Study Guides: Working Class, undated (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Study Tours, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Teachers, 1981 (Box 230, Folder 24)
  - Theoretical Articles by Others, 1992 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Theoretical Materials, 1987-1989 (Box 139, Folder 10-11)
  - Winston Enrollment Outlines, 1989 (Box 230, Folder 25)
  - Wilson School, undated (Box 237, Cassette 179)
  - Workers Circuit School, 1985-1988 (Box 140, Folder 1-7)
  - Workers Circuit School: Review, 1987 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Workers Circuit School: Teacher Outlines, 1977-1981 (Box 231, Folder 1-3)
  - Workers School, 1981 (Box 231, Folder 4-6)
  - Workers School: Outlines, 1940s (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Workers School: Outlines, 1982 (Box 231, Folder 7-8)
  - Workers School: Teacher Outlines and Schedules, 1978 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - Young Communist League: Seminar, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Youth School Enclosures, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 1-3)
  - Youth and Your Life, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Young Communist League, 1987-1990 (Box 141, Folder 5-7)
  - Young Workers Liberation League: Economy, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Young Workers Liberation League: National Class, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Young Workers Liberation League: National School, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Young Workers Liberation League: Seminar, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 11)
- Series V: Post-1991 Communist Party Split, 1991-2015; 37 Linear Feet in 77 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 4 cassette boxes; 71 audiocassettes; 2.54 Gigabytes in 1030 computer files
  This series documents Daniel Rubin's political work after he split with the CPUSA in 1991. Files from the 1990s largely relate to his organizing work with the Committees of Correspondence (CoC) and include correspondence, flyers and position papers from the organization as well as legal brief and statements from a lawsuit between CoC members and the Communist Party. Papers dated after 2000, largely consist of correspondence, drafts of reports and essays, and collected articles related to Rubin's organizing work for both the CoC and the CPUSA. These materials primarily focus on Brooklyn Clubs and New York State regional organizing. The series includes approximately 1136 digital files related to Rubin's work with the both CPUSA and CoC organizing, dated 2006-2015. Other materials in this series include correspondence and petitions related to development of the Atlantic Yards in Brooklyn and resistance to the construction of the Barclay's Center stadium. The series also includes extensive research files on international Jewish issues and the role of Jews in Communist Party.
  Born-digital records in this series consist of 3.5 gigabytes of emails, documents, and image files, which document Rubin's continued involvement in the CPUSA and his activism in local New York City politics. These files include drafts of Rubin's 2009 book, Can Capitalism Last: A Marxist Update; outlines, emails, and meeting notes from national, district, and local CPUSA organizing activities; and flyers, correspondence, and photos documenting Rubin's involvement in progressive political campaigns in Brooklyn and New York City. Rubin also saved biographical articles and obituaries honoring prominent Communist Party members. These biographical files include newspaper articles as well as transcripts of speeches honoring deceased Party members that Rubin collected for memorial events, the bulk of which are written about former Communist Party chairman Henry Winston.
  Files in this series are arranged alphabetically by name of organization and topic.
  Daniel Rubin left the Communist Party in 1991 along with many other Party members following political disagreements presented at the Party's 25th National Convention. Dissenting members formed the Committees of Correspondence, which later named the Committees of Correspondence for Democracy and Socialism. Beginning in 1992, Rubin and several other former Communist Party members were sued by the Communist Party over the wills of Rachel Freidenberg and Rosalind Tratchenberg who had bequeathed money to individual Party members. Party leadership claimed that money bequeathed by Freidenberg and Tratchenberg were intended for Communist Party and disputed Rubin's and other former member's intention to donate funds to the Committees of Correspondence. The cases were eventually settled in the late 1990s. Rubin renewed his membership in the Communist Party in 2000 and remained an active member in the party until his death in 2015.
  - African American Equality, 1989-1999 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - African American History, 2008, 2013-2015; TW_TAM_657_ER_1
  - Afro-American Affirmative Action, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Afro-American Affirmative Action AD: Initial Signers, 1996 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Afro-American Equality: Jim Jackson, Jim Steele, 1994 November 3 (Box 235, Cassette 73)
  - Afro-American Equality: Jim Jackson, Danny Rubin: Tape 1, 1993 December 22 (Box 235, Cassette 71)
  - Afro-American Equality: Tape 2, 1993 December 22 (Box 235, Cassette 72)
  - Afro-American Equality: MDG: Discussion, 1998 May 24 (Box 235, Cassette 75-76)
  - Afro-American Equality Affirmative Action AD: Letter to Thousands and Other Materials, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Afro-American Equality Affirmative Action AD: Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Afro-American Equality Affirmative Action AD: Letters, Cards, and AD Text, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Afro-American Equality Affirmative Action AD: Lists for Mailings, 1995-1996 (Box 142, Folder 4-5)
  - Afro-American Equality Affirmative Action AD: New York Times, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Afro-American Equality Affirmative Action AD: Preparation of AD, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 7-8)
  - Afro-American Equality Affirmative Action Project, 1995-1996 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Afro-American Equality Conference, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Afro-American Equality and CPUSA: Jackson, Diskin, Steele, Rubin, 1993 December 22 (Box 235, Cassette 70)
  - Afro-American Statement, circa 1999 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Americans with Disabilities Event Photographs, 2006; TW_TAM_657_ER_2
  - Angela Davis, 1998 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Communism, 1997 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Iraq War Protest Photographs, 2006; TW_TAM_657_ER_3
  - Anti-Semitism and Zionism Book, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Semitism and Zionism Book: Introduction, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 8-9)
  - Anti-Semitism and Zionism: College Students, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Semitism and Zionism: Marxist Writings, 2002-2003, 2007, 2010
    - Paper Materials (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_4
  - Aptheker, Herbert, 2001-2006 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Articles by Daniel Rubin: Typescripts, 1959-2013
    - Paper Materials (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_5
  - Articles Distributed or Published by Daniel Rubin, 1976-1992 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Yards, 2004-2009 (Box 144, Folder 4-7)
  - Atlantic Yards, 2005-2008 (Box 145, Folder 1-2)
  - Atlantic Yards: Affordable Housing, 2006 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Yards: Affordable Housing: Fifth Avenue Committee, 2006 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Yards: Brooklyn Community Organizations: Flyers, 2004 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Yards: Bulletins, undated (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Yards: Canvassing Materials: Chris Owens Candidacy, 2006 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Yards: Correspondence with Letitia James, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Yards: Develop Don't Destroy Brooklyn Discussion List and Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 145, Folder 9-11)
  - Atlantic Yards: Develop Don't Destroy Brooklyn Fundraiser, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Yards: Development, 2006 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Yards: Flyers, 2004 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Yards: Flyer Draft, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Yards: Housing, 2005-2006 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Yards: Statement on Environmental Impact of Atlantic Yards, by Daniel Rubin, circa 2005 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Biographies, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Biographies and Obituaries, 1997-2001 (Box 146, Folder 7-10)
  - Biographies and Obituaries, 2005-2008 (Box 147, Folder 1-2)
  - Black Radical Congress, 1997-1999 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Brecht Forum, 1998-2000 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Brodine: Wikipedia, 2013 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Periodicals, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Can Capitalism Last?: A Marxist Update by Daniel Rubin, 2009-2011
    - Paper Materials (Box 147, Folder 7-8)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_6
  - Can Capitalism Last?: Book Edits, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Can Capitalism Last?: Notes on Book, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Can Capitalism Last?: Sales, Mail, Etc., 2009 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Children's Literature, undated (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - China, 1997-2000 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - China: Communist Party, 2001-2006 (Box 148, Folder 2-3)
  - Chisholm, Shirley: Photographs, 2006; TW_TAM_657_ER_32
  - Civil Liberties, 1993-1999 (Box 148, Folder 4-5)
  - Class, Race, and Gender, 2001 (Box 148, Folder 6-7)
  - Class, Race, Gender: MDG, 2001 March 5 (Box 235, Cassette 67-69)
  - Cliff and Debt Ceiling (clipping), 2013 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Club Membership (Political Affairs, People's Weekly World, etc.), 2002 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Collected Ephemera: International Labor Hall of Fame, 2011 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Black Congress (CBC): Caring Majority Alternative Budget, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Committees of Correspondence, 2011-2014 (Box 149, Folder 1-3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: African American Affirmative Action Ad Books: Funds, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: African American Affirmative Action Ad Lists, 1995-1997 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Committees of Correspondence: African American Affirmative Action Ad: Listing Process, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Committees of Correspondence: African American Equality Outline, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Committees of Correspondence: African American Equality: Prior Ads and Articles, 1995-1998 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Brooklyn, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Business Funds, 1995-1996 (Box 149, Folder 10-11)
  - Committees of Correspondence: CPUSA Lawsuit, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Committees of Correspondence: CCDS, 2001 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Concert, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Conference, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Conference Agenda, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Conference Arrangement of Transport, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Conference Documents, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Convention, 2nd, 1996 (Box 150, Folder 5-6)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Correspondence, 2010 May (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Correspondence Regarding Memorials, 2011-2012 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Declaration of Purposes, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Discussion, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 10-12)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Discussion, 1992 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Discussion, Educational, and Research Committee, 1992 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Documents on Organization, 1992 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Economic Living Wage, 1996 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Education, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Education Activity Working Committee and Other Material, 1995 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Education: Finished Outlines, 1995 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Education: Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Education Project, 2002 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Educational Activity Working Committee, 1995 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Election Procedure, 1994 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Elections Resolution, 2000 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Elections Resolution, 2000 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Flyers, 2003-2007 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Funds, 1998, undated (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: General, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Globalization, 2001 (Box 152, Folder 5-6)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Goals and Principles, 1994-1995 (Box 152, Folder 7-8)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Implementation, 1992 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Issues, 1999 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Issues, 1999 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Leadership, 1992 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Committees of Correspondence: "Lessons from the Past", 1992 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Living Wage, 1998-1999 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Materials on Transnational Corporations, 1995 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Committees of Correspondence: National, 1995-1997 (Box 153, Folder 6-7)
  - Committees of Correspondence: National, 1992-2013 (Box 154, Folder 1-5)
  - Committees of Correspondence: National Coordinating Committee, 1995 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Committees of Correspondence: New York, 1994-2002 (Box 154, Folder 7-9)
  - Committees of Correspondence: New York, 1994-1997 (Box 155, Folder 1-3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: New York Structure, 1993 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Northern California and Other Areas, 1992-1993 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Organization Discussion, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 6-7)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Philadelphia, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Policies, 2000-2001 (Box 155, Folder 9-10)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Party, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Press Freedom, 1992 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Press Release, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Prioritizing, 1995 (Box 156, Folder 2-3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Publications, 1992 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Puerto Rico and Mexican Workers, 1996 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Retreat, 1991-1992 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Rubin on New York Organizational Structure, 1993 (Box 156, Folder 7-8)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Rubin Strategy, 1992 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Rubin Strategy: Lesson Original, 1992 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Socialism Discussion, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Strategy and Tactics, 1998-2001 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Strategy and Tactics: Rubin Original, undated (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Topics, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 2-3)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Working Class, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Workshops, 1992 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Committees of Correspondence: Youth, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party: 21st Century Socialism, 2011 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: African American History: Forum Example, undated (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party: Archives Case, 2002 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club, 2005-2015
    - Paper Materials (Box 157, Folder 10-12)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_7
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club, 2004-2015 (Box 158, Folder 1-7)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Agenda, 2003-2011, 2013
    - Paper Materials (Box 158, Folder 8-9)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_8
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Better World Awards, 2008-2013
    - Paper Materials (Box 158, Folder 10-11, Box 159, Folder 1-3)
    - Digital Materials, TW_TAM_657_ER_9
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Better World Awards: Chris Owens, 2012 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Better World Awards Luncheon, 2012 (Box 159, Folder 5-6)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Better World Awards: Letitia James Invitation, 2009 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Conference, 2003-2011 (Box 159, Folder 8-11)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Conference, 2007-2009 (Box 160, Folder 1-3)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Conference: Flyers, 2005 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Conference Invitation and Club Review, 2012 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Correspondence, 2010-2013 (Box 160, Folder 6-15)
  - Communist Party: Brooklyn Club: Correspondence, 2010-2013 (Box 161, Folder 1-7)
  - Communist Party: Discussion Group: Marxist Method, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 8)